(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.1",
"generated_at": "2026-08-13T21:20:39.581168",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
青くて澄んだ空をぎゅっと抱きしめて
Holding the blue, clear sky tight,
今日も快晴だ
It's clear weather today too.
「知らない」はきっと怖くて 「わかる」はきっと安心できる
"Not knowing" is surely scary, and "knowing" brings relief.
でも私が選ぶのは「ありえない」の向こう側
But what I choose is beyond the "impossible".
青くて澄んだ空を胸いっぱい吸い込んで 透明になるまで 声を鳴らし
Inhaling the blue, clear sky deep into my chest,
letting my voice ring out until I become transparent,
私が誰かを照らせるなら 誰かの救いになったら
If I can illuminate someone, if I can become someone's salvation,
奇跡の一つでも起こせるような気がするよ
I feel like I could make even a miracle happen.
動かなかった足を 今踏み出したと思える
Feeling like I've taken a step with feet that wouldn't move.
ひとりではできなかったこと
Things I couldn't do all by myself—
やっちゃよ、やっちゃよ、いっせーのーで！
Let's do it, let's do it, ready, go!
ぎゅっともっとさ、ぶっ飛んでいくぞ
I'm gonna blast off even further,
心の殻じゃしゃぎりゃまだまだ！
Breaking out of my shell, I'm still not done partying!
でも一歩一歩って進んでいくぞ
But step by step, we keep moving forward,
これが我らの第一歩！
This is our very first step!
ちゃんと見ていてくださいな！
Make sure you're watching me properly!
転んだり迷ったり浮き足立って
Stumbling, getting lost, getting flustered—
もうちょっと好きになってくださいませ
Please come to love me just a little more.
努力せず空回り 原点なんてのはございません
Working hard without results? There's no such starting point for us.
飛んでいきな
Fly on away,
めちゃくちゃに進め 年取るでしょ...
Move forward wildly as we grow older...
ファイヤー！イェー！
Fire! Yeah!
もしや今とてもいい感じ？
Could this moment be feeling just right?
もっとギア上げだっていい感じ！
It's even better if we crank up the gear more!
今日という日は
Today is—
だからめいっぱい声を出してみよう Let's go! せーの！
So let's raise our voices to the max! Let's go! Ready, go!
世界中大きく！
Make it big across the world!
いいよ、もっともう1回！
Alright, once more!
思い切り楽しく！
Have fun to your heart's content!
あー、めちゃくちゃ最高！
Ah, absolutely the best!
少しもやっていなかった未来に
Into a future we hadn't even attempted before,
今なら期待と勘違いしちゃってみる
Now I'll dare mistake it for expectation.
やっちゃよ、やっちゃよ、いっせーのーで！
Let's do it, let's do it, ready, go!
一歩一歩って突っ込むものの
Even as we charge in step by step,
どんどん待ってるでっかい世界に暗々裏
Deeply hidden within the vast world waiting for us,
でも一歩一歩大切にするぞ
But we'll cherish every single step forward.
それが我らの第一歩！
That is our very first step!
行くぞ、行くぞ、ぶっ飛んでいくぞ
Let's go, let's go, blasting off further!
心の殻じゃしゃぎりゃもうすぐ！
Breaking out of our shells, we'll reach it soon!
その一歩一歩を楽しみでいくぞ それじゃみんなで第一歩！
Enjoying every step along the way—now everyone, take that first step!
ちゃんと見ていてくださいな！転んだり迷ったり浮き足立って
Make sure you're watching me! Stumbling, getting lost, getting flustered,
もうちょっと好きになってくださいませ 努力せず空回り 原点なんてのはございません
Please come to love me just a little more. Working hard without results? There's no such starting point.
ずっと見ていてくださいな 育ってる、走ってる、未来が待ってる
Keep watching over me forever. Growing, running, the future is waiting.
予想外もご覧くださいませ 止めの時の頃に退屈なんてのはございません
Take a look at the unexpected too. There's never a dull moment at the final hour.
飛んでいきな めちゃくちゃに進め 年取るでしょ...
Fly on away, move forward wildly as we grow older...
あー、いっそ、フィーバー、イェー！
Ah, simply fever, yeah!
こんな狭い海の中 外のプライベートクルーズ回って
Cruising around outside in a private yacht within this narrow sea,
惚けた風采に抵抗もできずに 中に潜っていく
Unable to resist your dazed appearance, diving deeper inside.
ゆっくり髪をかき上げる 君を見ればもう鼓動
Seeing you slowly run your fingers through your hair makes my heart beat—
君と僕の時間はずっとなんか僕だけやっててた
Our time together—somehow I was the only one going on and on...
気を抜くとすぐに 歪んだ重力は
The moment I let my guard down, distorted gravity
何もかも呑み込んでよ
Swallows up everything and anything.
へいへい連れ去ってよ この常識がもっと濁ってんだ果ての無い
Hey hey, whisk me away! This common sense is growing even more turbid, endless—
街の血と壊して君の遺伝子で
Shattering the city's blood with your genetics,
バイバイテクノロジーで 滲んで絡みこんで無尽蔵に 愛し合えただけが終わり
With bye-bye technology, blurring, entangling, infinitely—only loving each other is the end.
ゆっくり髪をかき上げる 君を見れば鼓動
Seeing you slowly run your fingers through your hair makes my heart beat—
君を見ては鼓動 早くなる
Seeing you makes my heart beat faster.
ずっと昔から続く最大の謎
The greatest mystery continuing from long ago—
みんな放置して愛し合ってさ
Everyone ignores it and just loves each other.
まったくのゼロから生まれたこの感情
This emotion born entirely from zero—
対象性破れちゃったよ
Symmetry has broken down completely.
青くて澄んだ空をぎゅっと抱きしめて
Holding the clear blue sky tightly,
今日も快晴だ
today is clear weather too.
「知らない」はきっと怖くて
"Not knowing" is surely frightening,
「わかる」はきっと安心できる
and "understanding" brings sure relief.
でも私が選ぶのは「ありえない」の向こう側
But what I choose is beyond the "impossible".
青くて澄んだ空を胸いっぱいに吸い込んで
Breathing in the clear blue sky with all my heart,
透明になるまで 声を鳴らせ
I let my voice ring out until I become transparent.
私が誰かを照らせるなら
If I can shine a light on someone,
誰かの救いになったら
if I can become someone's salvation,
奇跡の一つでも起こせそうな気がするよ
I feel like I could work even a single miracle.
歌声は溶けて朝になる
My singing voice melts into morning,
悲しみごと抱いて微熱を帯びる
embracing even the sorrow while carrying a slight fever.
そうだ、この気持ちに名前を付けるなら
That's right, if I were to give this feeling a name...
「アツイ」はきっと端から冷めて
"Hot" surely cools from the edges,
「定番」になれば御の字
and if it becomes a "classic," that's more than enough.
せっかくならみんなでさ
Since we have the chance,
笑った顔見せ合っていこうぜ
let's all show each other our smiling faces.
青くて春な夢を胸いっぱいに背負い込んで
Carrying a youthful dream in my chest to the fullest,
熟れたその分だけ 思い出となれ
may it become memories in proportion to how ripe it has grown.
私がただ幸せだったら
If I had simply been happy,
悔やむことさえなかったら
if there had been nothing to regret,
心に眠った衝動に気付くこともないから
I wouldn't even have noticed the impulse sleeping in my heart,
歌声は涙に寄り添う
so my singing voice nestles close to tears.
ときめきごと抱いて微熱を帯びる
Embracing every flutter of excitement while carrying a slight fever.
そうだ、この気持ちに名前を付けるなら
That's right, if I were to give this feeling a name...
花が咲けば枯れていく
Flowers bloom and wither away,
種を蒔けば宿っていく
seeds are sown and take root;
運命の意味なんて元から無いんじゃない?
wasn't there never any meaning to destiny to begin with?
咲き誇れ 散り笑え
Bloom proudly, scatter and smile.
私が誰かを照らせるなら
If I can shine a light on someone,
誰かの救いになったら
if I can become someone's salvation,
奇跡の一つでも起こせそうな気がするよ
I feel like I could work even a single miracle.
歌声は溶けて朝になる
My singing voice melts into morning,
悲しみごと抱いて微熱を帯びる
embracing even the sorrow while carrying a slight fever.
空が温かくてきれいだ
The sky is warm and beautiful.
私はなんだか小粒な
Somehow, I found this humble feeling
この気持ちが愛おしくて大好きだったんだ
so endearing and loved it so much.
名前のないこの気持ちを
This nameless feeling...
青くて澄んだ空をぎゅっと抱きしめて
Holding the clear blue sky tightly,
今日も快晴だ
today is clear weather too.
「知らない」はきっと怖くて
"Not knowing" is surely frightening,
「わかる」はきっと安心できる
and "understanding" brings sure relief.
でも私が選ぶのは「ありえない」の向こう側
But what I choose is beyond the "impossible".
青くて澄んだ空を胸いっぱいに吸い込んで
Breathing in the clear blue sky with all my heart,
透明になるまで 声を鳴らせ
I let my voice ring out until I become transparent.
私が誰かを照らせるなら
If I can shine a light on someone,
誰かの救いになったら
if I can become someone's salvation,
奇跡の一つでも起こせそうな気がするよ
I feel like I could work even a single miracle.
歌声は溶けて朝になる
My singing voice melts into morning,
悲しみごと抱いて微熱を帯びる
embracing even the sorrow while carrying a slight fever.
そうだ、この気持ちに名前を付けるなら
That's right, if I were to give this feeling a name...
「アツイ」はきっと端から冷めて
"Hot" surely cools from the edges,
「定番」になれば御の字
and if it becomes a "classic," that's more than enough.
せっかくならみんなでさ
Since we have the chance,
笑った顔見せ合っていこうぜ
let's all show each other our smiling faces.
青くて春な夢を胸いっぱいに背負い込んで
Carrying a youthful dream in my chest to the fullest,
熟れたその分だけ 思い出となれ
may it become memories in proportion to how ripe it has grown.
私がただ幸せだったら
If I had simply been happy,
悔やむことさえなかったら
if there had been nothing to regret,
心に眠った衝動に気付くこともないから
I wouldn't even have noticed the impulse sleeping in my heart,
歌声は涙に寄り添う
so my singing voice nestles close to tears.
ときめきごと抱いて微熱を帯びる
Embracing every flutter of excitement while carrying a slight fever.
そうだ、この気持ちに名前を付けるなら
That's right, if I were to give this feeling a name...
花が咲けば枯れていく
Flowers bloom and wither away,
種を蒔けば宿っていく
seeds are sown and take root;
運命の意味なんて元から無いんじゃない?
wasn't there never any meaning to destiny to begin with?
咲き誇れ 散り笑え
Bloom proudly, scatter and smile.
私が誰かを照らせるなら
If I can shine a light on someone,
誰かの救いになったら
if I can become someone's salvation,
奇跡の一つでも起こせそうな気がするよ
I feel like I could work even a single miracle.
歌声は溶けて朝になる
My singing voice melts into morning,
悲しみごと抱いて微熱を帯びる
embracing even the sorrow while carrying a slight fever.
空が温かくてきれいだ
The sky is warm and beautiful.
私はなんだか小粒な
Somehow, I found this humble feeling
この気持ちが愛おしくて大好きだったんだ
so endearing and loved it so much.
名前のないこの気持ちを
This nameless feeling...
青くて澄んだ空をぎゅっと抱きしめて
Holding the clear blue sky tightly,
今日も快晴だ
today is clear weather too.
「知らない」はきっと怖くて
"Not knowing" is surely frightening,
「わかる」はきっと安心できる
and "understanding" brings sure relief.
でも私が選ぶのは「ありえない」の向こう側
But what I choose is beyond the "impossible".
青くて澄んだ空を胸いっぱいに吸い込んで
Breathing in the clear blue sky with all my heart,
透明になるまで 声を鳴らせ
I let my voice ring out until I become transparent.
私が誰かを照らせるなら
If I can shine a light on someone,
誰かの救いになったら
if I can become someone's salvation,
奇跡の一つでも起こせそうな気がするよ
I feel like I could work even a single miracle.
歌声は溶けて朝になる
My singing voice melts into morning,
悲しみごと抱いて微熱を帯びる
embracing even the sorrow while carrying a slight fever.
そうだ、この気持ちに名前を付けるなら
That's right, if I were to give this feeling a name...
「アツイ」はきっと端から冷めて
"Hot" surely cools from the edges,
「定番」になれば御の字
and if it becomes a "classic," that's more than enough.
せっかくならみんなでさ
Since we have the chance,
笑った顔見せ合っていこうぜ
let's all show each other our smiling faces.
青くて春な夢を胸いっぱいに背負い込んで
Carrying a youthful dream in my chest to the fullest,
熟れたその分だけ 思い出となれ
may it become memories in proportion to how ripe it has grown.
私がただ幸せだったら
If I had simply been happy,
悔やむことさえなかったら
if there had been nothing to regret,
心に眠った衝動に気付くこともないから
I wouldn't even have noticed the impulse sleeping in my heart,
歌声は涙に寄り添う
so my singing voice nestles close to tears.
ときめきごと抱いて微熱を帯びる
Embracing every flutter of excitement while carrying a slight fever.
そうだ、この気持ちに名前を付けるなら
That's right, if I were to give this feeling a name...
花が咲けば枯れていく
Flowers bloom and wither away,
種を蒔けば宿っていく
seeds are sown and take root;
運命の意味なんて元から無いんじゃない?
wasn't there never any meaning to destiny to begin with?
咲き誇れ 散り笑え
Bloom proudly, scatter and smile.
私が誰かを照らせるなら
If I can shine a light on someone,
誰かの救いになったら
if I can become someone's salvation,
奇跡の一つでも起こせそうな気がするよ
I feel like I could work even a single miracle.
歌声は溶けて朝になる
My singing voice melts into morning,
悲しみごと抱いて微熱を帯びる
embracing even the sorrow while carrying a slight fever.
いけないんだ もう知らない
I shouldn't be doing this, I don't know anymore
知らない言葉を覚えていくたび
Each time I learn new words
いけないんだ もう知らない
I shouldn't be doing this, I don't know anymore
好きを思わせて
Making me feel in love
すれ違うのもフェアじゃない
Passing each other by isn't fair either
いけないんだ もう知らない
I shouldn't be doing this, I don't know anymore
知らない言葉を覚えていくたび
Each time I learn new words
いけないんだ もう知らない
I shouldn't be doing this, I don't know anymore
好きを思わせて
Making me feel in love
すれ違うのもフェアじゃない
Passing each other by isn't fair either
いけないんだ もう知らない
I shouldn't be doing this, I don't know anymore
知らない言葉を覚えていくたび
Each time I learn new words
いけないんだ もう知らない
I shouldn't be doing this, I don't know anymore
好きを思わせて
Making me feel in love
すれ違うのもフェアじゃない
Passing each other by isn't fair either
いけないんだ もう知らない
I shouldn't be doing this, I don't know anymore
知らない言葉を覚えていくたび
Each time I learn new words
いけないんだ もう知らない
I shouldn't be doing this, I don't know anymore
好きを思わせて
Making me feel in love
すれ違うのもフェアじゃない
Passing each other by isn't fair either
本日は、ソラAZメジャーデビューライブ「First Gravity」、@(アット)クラブチッタに来て、ご来場いただきまして、誠にありがとうございます。
Thank you very much for coming to the SorAZ Major Debut Live 'First Gravity' at Club CITT'a today.
開演に先立ちまして、ソラマメの皆様にお願いしたいことをお伝えします。
Before the concert starts, we would like to ask a few things of the Soramame.
客席内でのモッシュ、ダイブ等の危険行為は禁止となっております。
Mosh pits, crowdsurfing, and other dangerous activities in the seating area are prohibited.
以上のことが守られない場合は、公演を一時中断、もしくは中止させていただく可能性がございます。
If these rules are not followed, the performance may be temporarily suspended or canceled.
ペンライトは周りのお客様のご迷惑にならないよう、ご配慮お願いいたします。
Please be considerate with your penlights so as not to disturb surrounding guests.
頭の上にだしたり、大きく左右に振り回すと後ろのお客様や周りのお客様のご迷惑となる場合がございます。
Holding them above your head or swinging them widely left and right may disturb guests behind or around you.
スタッフが注意させていただく場合がございますので、ご容赦ください。
Staff may caution you, so your understanding is appreciated.
本公演は映像配信および写真撮影用のカメラが会場内に入り、お客様の様子が映り込む場合がございます。
Cameras for video streaming and photography will be inside the venue for this performance, and audience members may appear on camera.
これらの映像や写真はプロモーション等に使用される可能性がありますので、あらかじめご容赦ください。
Please understand in advance that these footage and photos may be used for promotions and such.
客席内での携帯電話、スマートフォンの利用は禁止です。
The use of mobile phones and smartphones inside the seating area is prohibited.
携帯電話や音の鳴る機械の電源は予めお切りいただきますようお願い申し上げます。
Please make sure to turn off the power of mobile phones and sound-making devices in advance.
動画による撮影、録音、録画を固くお断りします。
Photography, audio recording, and video recording are strictly prohibited.
万が一発見した場合は、データ削除の上、退場していただく場合がございます。
If discovered, you may be asked to delete your data and leave.
最後に、ライブの途中で具合が悪くなったりしたら、お近くのスタッフにお声がけください。
Finally, if you feel unwell during the live, please speak to nearby staff.
また、地震、火事などの非常時は、慌てずスタッフの誘導に従って避難していただきますよう、お願いいたします。
In case of emergencies like earthquakes or fires, please evacuate calmly following staff guidance.
配信でご視聴のお客へ、本ライブの録音、録画、ミラー配信や違法アップロードは固くお断りします。
To viewers watching the stream, recording, screen-capturing, mirror streaming, or illegal uploading is strictly prohibited.
本ライブの録音、録画、ミラー配信や違法アップロードは固くお断りします。
Recording, mirror streaming, and illegal uploading of this live are strictly prohibited.
その代わり、スクリーンショットを撮影して画像とともにSNSに投稿していただくことは大歓迎です。
Instead, taking screenshots and posting them with images on SNS is very welcome.
本公演のハッシュタグは、「そらあずぐらびティ」となります。
The hashtag for this performance is "#SoraAZGravity".
それでは公演開始まで今しばらくお待ちください。
Please wait a little longer until the performance begins.
電波テンポアップして絶賛感電中！
The radio wave tempo has increased and the excitement is electrifying!
知らない言葉を覚えていくたび
As I learn words I never knew,
みんな聞こえてるー？聞こえてる！ありがとう！
Can everyone hear me? We can hear you! Thank you!
これの影ナレでございます！
This is today's voiceover announcement!
まだ疲れてないよね？
You're not tired yet, right?
夜っていう程夜でもないのかな？
Is it even late enough to call it night?
夜、夜公演ですよ。
Night, it's the night show.
昼公演をみんな越えられますよね？
Everyone can surpass the day show, right?
今初めて見るって人ももちろんいると思うので、そういう子たちは新鮮な気持ちで楽しんでもらえたら嬉しいなって思います。
Of course, there are people seeing this for the first time, so I hope they can enjoy it with a fresh feeling.
わかりましたかー？
Did you understand?
はーい！
Yay!
ハッシュタグはそらあずぐらびティでポストしてください。はい、そらまめのみんな仲良く楽しくライブを楽しんでください。
Please post with the hashtag #SoraAZGravity. Yes, Soramame everyone, get along well and enjoy the live.
それじゃあちょっと待っててね！偉いぞー！
Well then, wait a little bit! Good job!
待ってるー！
Waiting for you!
まだ見ぬ遠く新しい物語
A brand new story to a yet-unseen distant place
三つ目の朝が来るまで
until the third morning comes
響く 光 君の光が
Resonating, glowing, your light
まさかなの ともるこの星も かななたの宇宙
Even this star lighting up... space...
描けなかったような物語が生まれる 方程式に導かれて
Stories we never imagined we could sketch are born, guided by equations.
この音が聞こえた時 今 君が感じている心拍数 共鳴していく
When this sound is heard, the heart rate you are feeling right now is resonating.
感情 友情 愛情 当たり前に抱ける奇跡 同じ世界で巡り会えたのは 必然の未来
Emotion, friendship, affection—the miracle of naturally holding them, meeting in the same world is an inevitable future.
マグネットの手を触ればほらつながってるから 星座のようにマグネット またきっとどんな場所でも惹かれ合うさだめのままで
If you touch the magnetic hands, look, we're connected, like a constellation, magnet. Once again, no matter where, drawn together as destined.
まさかなころ なおくとりて探りの宇宙
Unbelievable, taking a path of exploration in space
不完全だってさ かけた月のような 誰も知らない夢になる
Even if imperfect, like a waning moon, it becomes a dream nobody knows.
予測不可能な遭遇さ 指と指合わせた時 今 ここで混ざり合う潮津
Unpredictable encounter—when fingers meet, right here, tides mix.
電波テンポアップして絶賛感電中!
up the tempo of the frequency for shocking electricity!
おもかげの中 手を伸ばすの
i reach my hand toward the traces they leave.
私が私の事を愛して
i guess i’m just not getting all the big commotion
ひびく ふれる ひかる
touching, feeling, shining
電波テンポアップして絶賛感電中!
up the tempo of the frequency for shocking electricity!
おもかげの中 手を伸ばすの
i reach my hand toward the traces they leave.
私が私の事を愛して
i guess i’m just not getting all the big commotion
ひびく ふれる ひかる
touching, feeling, shining
電波テンポアップして絶賛感電中!
up the tempo of the frequency for shocking electricity!
おもかげの中 手を伸ばすの
i reach my hand toward the traces they leave.
私が私の事を愛して
i guess i’m just not getting all the big commotion
ひびく ふれる ひかる
touching, feeling, shining
電波テンポアップして絶賛感電中!
up the tempo of the frequency for shocking electricity!
おもかげの中 手を伸ばすの
i reach my hand toward the traces they leave.
私が私の事を愛して
i guess i’m just not getting all the big commotion
ひびく ふれる ひかる
touching, feeling, shining
電波テンポアップして絶賛感電中!
up the tempo of the frequency for shocking electricity!
おもかげの中 手を伸ばすの
i reach my hand toward the traces they leave.
私が私の事を愛して
i guess i’m just not getting all the big commotion
ひびく ふれる ひかる
touching, feeling, shining
電波テンポアップして絶賛感電中!
up the tempo of the frequency for shocking electricity!
おもかげの中 手を伸ばすの
i reach my hand toward the traces they leave.
生まれ初めて書いたのはなんて字だったかな
I wonder what character I wrote the very first time I was born.
いつも何かを伝えるように歌ってる
Singing so as to always convey something,
飲み込んだ想い青い空に飛ばせ
sending the swallowed feelings up into the blue sky.
つながるメロディ 流れる星に
A connecting melody, turning into shooting stars,
変わってく 君のために歌うよ
changing as I sing for you.
君に届くようにと
Reaching out to you,
輝きは世界軸を越えて
brilliance transcends the axis of the world.
確かにここで重ね合えた鼓動
The heartbeat we surely shared and overlapped right here,
振り合う音が光になって降り注ぐ
the sounds of our crossing become light and pour down.
この一瞬が永遠へと煌めいては
This single moment sparkles into eternity,
色づいていく 君と描いた世界
coloring the world we painted together.
君と描く音が飛び立つ
The sound we paint together takes flight,
切なすぎる心のくまで
all the way to the depths of our painful hearts.
知らない映画なのに涙を流すのは
Shedding tears at an unfamiliar movie
ドラマティックが足りないからよ
is because there isn't enough drama.
知らない言葉を覚えていくたび
Every time I learn words I didn't know,
面影のなか手を伸ばすのだけれど
I reach out within my memories, but...
生まれ初めて書いたのはなんて字だったかな
I wonder what character I wrote the very first time I was born.
いつも何かを伝えるように歌ってる
Singing so as to always convey something,
飲み込んだ想い青い空に飛ばせ
sending the swallowed feelings up into the blue sky.
つながるメロディ 流れる星に
A connecting melody, turning into shooting stars,
変わってく 君のために歌うよ
changing as I sing for you.
君に届くようにと
Reaching out to you,
輝きは世界軸を越えて
brilliance transcends the axis of the world.
確かにここで重ね合えた鼓動
The heartbeat we surely shared and overlapped right here,
振り合う音が光になって降り注ぐ
the sounds of our crossing become light and pour down.
この一瞬が永遠へと煌めいては
This single moment sparkles into eternity,
色づいていく 君と描いた世界
coloring the world we painted together.
君と描く音が飛び立つ
The sound we paint together takes flight,
切なすぎる心のくまで
all the way to the depths of our painful hearts.
知らない映画なのに涙を流すのは
Shedding tears at an unfamiliar movie
ドラマティックが足りないからよ
is because there isn't enough drama.
知らない言葉を覚えていくたび
Every time I learn words I didn't know,
面影のなか手を伸ばすのだけれど
I reach out within my memories, but...
生まれ初めて書いたのはなんて字だったかな
I wonder what character I wrote the very first time I was born.
いつも何かを伝えるように歌ってる
Singing so as to always convey something,
飲み込んだ想い青い空に飛ばせ
sending the swallowed feelings up into the blue sky.
つながるメロディ 流れる星に
A connecting melody, turning into shooting stars,
変わってく 君のために歌うよ
changing as I sing for you.
君に届くようにと
Reaching out to you,
輝きは世界軸を越えて
brilliance transcends the axis of the world.
確かにここで重ね合えた鼓動
The heartbeat we surely shared and overlapped right here,
振り合う音が光になって降り注ぐ
the sounds of our crossing become light and pour down.
この一瞬が永遠へと煌めいては
This single moment sparkles into eternity,
色づいていく 君と描いた世界
coloring the world we painted together.
君と描く音が飛び立つ
The sound we paint together takes flight,
切なすぎる心のくまで
all the way to the depths of our painful hearts.
知らない映画なのに涙を流すのは
Shedding tears at an unfamiliar movie
ドラマティックが足りないからよ
is because there isn't enough drama.
知らない言葉を覚えていくたび
Every time I learn words I didn't know,
面影のなか手を伸ばすのだけれど
I reach out within my memories, but...
生まれ初めて書いたのはなんて字だったかな
I wonder what character I wrote the very first time I was born.
いつも何かを伝えるように歌ってる
Singing so as to always convey something,
飲み込んだ想い青い空に飛ばせ
sending the swallowed feelings up into the blue sky.
つながるメロディ 流れる星に
A connecting melody, turning into shooting stars,
変わってく 君のために歌うよ
changing as I sing for you.
君に届くようにと
Reaching out to you,
輝きは世界軸を越えて
brilliance transcends the axis of the world.
確かにここで重ね合えた鼓動
The heartbeat we surely shared and overlapped right here,
振り合う音が光になって降り注ぐ
the sounds of our crossing become light and pour down.
この一瞬が永遠へと煌めいては
This single moment sparkles into eternity,
色づいていく 君と描いた世界
coloring the world we painted together.
君と描く音が飛び立つ
The sound we paint together takes flight,
切なすぎる心のくまで
all the way to the depths of our painful hearts.
知らない映画なのに涙を流すのは
Shedding tears at an unfamiliar movie
ドラマティックが足りないからよ
is because there isn't enough drama.
知らない言葉を覚えていくたび
Every time I learn words I didn't know,
面影のなか手を伸ばすのだけれど
I reach out within my memories, but...
生まれ初めて書いたのはなんて字だったかな
I wonder what character I wrote the very first time I was born.
いつも何かを伝えるように歌ってる
Singing so as to always convey something,
飲み込んだ想い青い空に飛ばせ
sending the swallowed feelings up into the blue sky.
つながるメロディ 流れる星に
A connecting melody, turning into shooting stars,
変わってく 君のために歌うよ
changing as I sing for you.
君に届くようにと
Reaching out to you,
輝きは世界軸を越えて
brilliance transcends the axis of the world.
確かにここで重ね合えた鼓動
The heartbeat we surely shared and overlapped right here,
振り合う音が光になって降り注ぐ
the sounds of our crossing become light and pour down.
この一瞬が永遠へと煌めいては
This single moment sparkles into eternity,
色づいていく 君と描いた世界
coloring the world we painted together.
君と描く音が飛び立つ
The sound we paint together takes flight,
切なすぎる心のくまで
all the way to the depths of our painful hearts.
知らない映画なのに涙を流すのは
Shedding tears at an unfamiliar movie
ドラマティックが足りないからよ
is because there isn't enough drama.
知らない言葉を覚えていくたび
Every time I learn words I didn't know,
面影のなか手を伸ばすのだけれど
I reach out within my memories, but...
生まれ初めて書いたのはなんて字だったかな
I wonder what character I wrote the very first time I was born.
いつも何かを伝えるように歌ってる
Singing so as to always convey something.
私 が 私 の 事 を 愛して
I love myself
水滴 の 音 が 響く 宇宙 に 耳 を 澄ます
Listening closely to the sound of water droplets echoing in the universe
天の川 が 流れ着く 先 時空 を 超えて
Where the Milky Way flows, crossing space-time
水 の 惑星 が どこかで 煌めいて いる
A water planet is sparkling somewhere
飛沫 上げ ながら 泳ぐ 銀河 の 海
Swimming through the ocean of galaxies, raising splashes
名 も なき この 場所 で 開いた 衝動 の 花
In this nameless place, flowers of impulse bloomed
静かな 始まり を 告げる
Announcing a quiet beginning
幼い あこがれ が 確かな 熱 を 求めて
My childish longing sought a definite warmth
繰り返して いく 日々 に 背 を 向けて
Leaving behind days that repeat themselves
まだ 見えぬ 世界 へ 限界 を 超えて 行きたい
I want to go beyond limits into a world yet unseen
我ら の 宇宙 の はじまり は ( パパ ヤ )
The beginning of our universe (Papaya)
触れた 瞬間 アラ ラララ ( パパ ヤ )
The moment it touched, oh la la la (Papaya)
はぁ ～ 、 これ は 困った ！ 二度と もと に は 戻らない 大 ！ 爆 ！ 発 ！
Ha~, this is trouble! A great! Explosion! that will never return twice!
そして 星 が 生まれまして ( パパ ヤ )
And stars were born (Papaya)
明け方 の 一番星 は ( パパ ヤ )
The first star at dawn (Papaya)
あなた と 出会った ！
Met you!
これ は 次元 を 揺るがす 大 ！ 発 ！ 見 ！
This is a great! Discovery! that shakes dimensions!
このまま ハート 打ち上げて どこまでも たかい 宇宙 まで
Launch this heart as it is, to the endlessly high universe
「 めっちゅ 飛んじゃい タイッ ！ 」
"I want to fly away so much!"
さあ スター スター スタート 効きずいた この ラブ は
Now, Star Star Start, this cut love is
あなた が いないと 待ったなし で 超 ！ 新 ！ 星 ！
If you aren't here, no hesitation, a Super! Nova!
する ぞ ！？ ( オー ・ オ ・ オー ！)
Shall we do it? (Oh-oh-oh!)
しちゃう ぞ ？! ( オー ・ オ ・ オー ！)
Shall we do it?! (Oh-oh-oh!)
あなた に 言ってますっ ！
I'm telling you!
ドゥー ユアンダ スタンス 、 スタンス 、 スタンド あの 、 わかっている ？
Do you understand, stand, stand, hey, do you understand?
ほら 目 の 前 に ずっと ある 一 ！ 等 ！ 星 ！
Look, right in front of you, the everlasting First! Magnitude! Star!
みてる ？ ( オー ・ オ ・ オー ！)
Are you watching? (Oh-oh-oh!)
きーてる ？! ( オー ・ オ ・ オー ！)
Are you listening?! (Oh-oh-oh!)
この ビッグバン 気づいて ！！！！！！
Notice this Big Bang!!!!!!
( ナナナナ ナナナナ ナナナナ )
(Na-na-na-na Na-na-na-na Na-na Na-na-na)
愛 は 地球 くらい に 膨らんで こんなに なってん ぞ
Love has swelled up to the size of the Earth, it's gotten this big
( ナナナナ ナナナナ ナナナナ )
(Na-na-na-na Na-na-na-na Na-na Na-na-na)
そうさ 第三 の 惑星 は この とき の ため の スター ！
That's right, the third planet is the star for this exact moment!
我ら の 宇宙 の はじまり は ( パパ ヤ )
The beginning of our universe (Papaya)
触れた 瞬間 アラ ラララ ( パパ ヤ )
The moment it touched, oh la la la (Papaya)
はぁ ～ 、 これ は 困った ！
Ha~, this is trouble!
二度と もと に は 戻らない 大 ！ 爆 ！ 発 ！
A great! Explosion! that will never return twice!
そして 星 が 生まれまして ( パパ ヤ )
And stars were born (Papaya)
明け方 の 一番星 は ( パパ ヤ )
The first star at dawn (Papaya)
あなた と 出会った ！
Met you!
これ は 次元 を 揺るがす 大 ！ 発 ！ 見 ！
This is a great! Discovery! that shakes dimensions!
このまま ハート 打ち上げて どこまでも たかい 宇宙 まで
Launch this heart as it is, to the endlessly high universe
「 めっちゅ 飛んじゃい タイッ ！ 」
"I want to fly away so much!"
さあ スター スター スタート 効きずいた この ラブ は
Now, Star Star Start, this cut love is
あなた が いないと 待ったなし で 超 ！ 新 ！ 星 ！
If you aren't here, no hesitation, a Super! Nova!
する ぞ ！？ ( オー ・ オ ・ オー ！)
Shall we do it? (Oh-oh-oh!)
しちゃう ぞ ？! ( オー ・ オ ・ オー ！)
Shall we do it?! (Oh-oh-oh!)
あなた に 言ってますっ ！
I'm telling you!
ドゥー ユアンダ スタンス 、 スタンス 、 スタンド あの 、 わかっている ？
Do you understand, stand, stand, hey, do you understand?
ほら 目 の 前 に ずっと ある 一 ！ 等 ！ 星 ！
Look, right in front of you, the everlasting First! Magnitude! Star!
みてる ？ ( オー ・ オ ・ オー ！)
Are you watching? (Oh-oh-oh!)
きーてる ？! ( オー ・ オ ・ オー ！)
Are you listening?! (Oh-oh-oh!)
この ビッグバン 気づいて ！！！！！！
Notice this Big Bang!!!!!!
( ナナナナ ナナナナ ナナナナ )
(Na-na-na-na Na-na-na-na Na-na Na-na-na)
愛 は 地球 くらい に 膨らんで こんなに なってん ぞ
Love has swelled up to the size of the Earth, it's gotten this big
( ナナナナ ナナナナ ナナナナ )
(Na-na-na-na Na-na-na-na Na-na Na-na-na)
そうさ 第三 の 惑星 は この とき の ため の スター ！
That's right, the third planet is the star for this exact moment!
我ら の 宇宙 の はじまり は ( パパ ヤ )
The beginning of our universe (Papaya)
触れた 瞬間 アラ ラララ ( パパ ヤ )
The moment it touched, oh la la la (Papaya)
はぁ ～ 、 これ は 困った ！
Ha~, this is trouble!
二度と もと に は 戻らない 大 ！ 爆 ！ 発 ！
A great! Explosion! that will never return twice!
そして 星 が 生まれまして ( パパ ヤ )
And stars were born (Papaya)
せーのっ
One, two...
せーのっで！深呼吸
Take a deep breath!
はじまってくここから
It all starts right from here,
ready go！
ready go!
みんな来てくれてありがとう！
Thank you all for coming!
最高だよー！
You're the best!
大気圏突き抜けて
Piercing through the atmosphere,
イメージも歌声も
both our imagery and singing voice
意識を飛び越えて響く
transcend consciousness and resonate!
輝く
Shining...
電子の小宇宙
a micro-universe of electrons,
漂いめぐり会い
drifting and meeting by chance,
瞬間同期する
synchronizing in an instant—
キセキってgroovy
that's a miracle, groovy!
bpm高まって
With rising BPM,
クルクル回るみんな
everyone spins round and round,
まるですべてがミラーボール
just like a mirror ball.
わたしたちの夢のファーストブレス
This is our dream's first breath,
思い切り遊ぼう
let's play to our heart's content!
a to z空を駆け抜け
A to Z, running through the skies,
振り切っちゃってこう！
let's shake it all off and go!
化学反応で生み出すヒカリ
The light born from chemical reactions
今ここで繋がった
has connected right here and now.
照らして照らし合って
Shining and reflecting off each other,
せーのっで！うなづいて
one, two... give a nod!
はじまってくwonder
A wonder is beginning,
ready go！
ready go!
ドキドキタップして
Tap your excitement,
ひらくは新時代
and a new era opens up.
可能性その海は
The sea of possibilities
なんてamazing！
is simply amazing!
時代のエーテルに
Throbbing with excitement
ドキドキ伝播する
through the ether of the times,
解釈一致でしょ？
our interpretations match, right?
生きるってfantastic
Living is fantastic!
運命のシンコペーション
The syncopation of destiny
星屑のランウェイから
from the stardust runway—
投げるキラービート
throw out the killer beat.
未知の彼方光るフューチャーサイン
A future sign shining in the unknown,
キャッチしてgrowing up
catch it and keep growing up!
iとu奏でるのは
What i and u play together
ミラクルでいい？
can it be a miracle?
以心伝心でまるでテレパス
Like telepathy from heart to heart,
今という瞬間を
let's feel the present moment
感じて感じ合って
and share that feeling together.
せーのっで！深呼吸
One, two... take a deep breath!
見たことないwonder
A wonder we've never seen before,
キミと届くように…
hoping it reaches you...
オモイとオモイが作るセカイ
A world created by our feelings intertwining,
ここにあるここにいるよ
we are right here, right now.
歌おう歌えばひとつになれる
Let's sing—if we sing, we become one,
もっとなれるよ自由に
we can become even freer!
ようこそここはバイアスのかからない
Welcome, this is an unbiased
二人のexpo
expo for the two of us,
gonna be spacy
わたしたちの夢のファーストブレス
This is our dream's first breath,
思い切り遊ぼう
let's play to our heart's content!
a to z空を駆け抜け
A to Z, running through the skies,
振り切っちゃってgo！
let's shake it all off and go!
化学反応で生み出すヒカリ
The light born from chemical reactions
今ここで繋がった
has connected right here and now.
照らして照らし合って
Shining and reflecting off each other,
せーのっで！うなづいて
one, two... give a nod!
はじまってくwonder
A wonder is beginning,
ready go！
ready go!
自由にずっと憧れて 部屋を飛び出して
Dreaming freely all this time, I dashed out of my room,
理不尽な現実を嘆く日もあった
and there were days I lamented the unreasonable reality.
居場所のない私に 君は寄り添ってくれたね
To me, who had nowhere to belong, you stayed by my side.
今度は私が助け出すよ
This time, I'll rescue you.
世界が混ざっていく身体が火照っていく
The world is blending together, my body is burning up,
今 物語を欺け
Now, deceive the story!
あらすじには書かれていないこと
Things not written in the synopsis,
あとがきには収まらないこと
things that won't fit in the afterword—
運命にそっぽ向いて本当の願いを抱き締めよう
turn away from fate and hold close our true wishes.
手を取れ 史上最悪な伏線でも
Take my hand, even if it's history's worst foreshadowing;
君のすぐ隣で全力でもっと生きるんだ
right beside you, I'll live even harder with all my might.
手を取れ この残酷な現実で何度でも
Take my hand, no matter how many times in this cruel reality—
私たちは大丈夫 少しだけ強くなったんだ
we'll be fine, we've gotten just a little bit stronger.
諦めないから 信じよう、ずっと
We won't give up, let's keep believing forever.
一生懸命な君が 少し頑張り過ぎて
You, who always give your all, tried just a bit too hard,
辛くならないように 食べ泣き笑おう
so let's eat, cry, and laugh so it won't be too painful.
思い出が混ざっていく もう失くしたくはないんだ
Memories are blending together, I don't want to lose anything more.
喜怒哀楽とそれ以外も 全部本当の宝物
Joy, anger, sorrow, pleasure, and everything else are all genuine treasures.
物語の枠外に この気持ちを残そう
Let's leave these feelings outside the margins of the story.
あらかえ 史上最悪な伏線でも
Resist, even with history's worst foreshadowing;
君のすぐ隣で何千回だって笑うんだ
right beside you, I'll laugh thousands of times over.
頑張れ なんて言葉は今更言わないから
I won't say things like "do your best" anymore now.
私たちは大丈夫 もう背中を預けたんだ
We'll be fine, we've already entrusted our backs to each other.
最後まで君を信じよう、ずっと
Let's keep believing in you until the very end.
Make a Story Remake a Story 左右非対称の世界
Make a Story, Remake a Story, a left-right asymmetric world.
矛盾する理さえ愛して
Love even the contradictory logic,
まだ生きていこう それで間違っていこう 何度も
and keep on living, making mistakes along the way, again and again.
世界が混ざっていく 身体が火照っていく
The world is blending together, my body is burning up,
今 物語を欺け
Now, deceive the story!
あらすじには書かれていないこと
Things not written in the synopsis,
あとがきには収まらないこと
things that won't fit in the afterword—
運命にそっぽ向いて本当の願いを抱き締めよう
turn away from fate and hold close our true wishes.
手を取れ 史上最悪な伏線でも
Take my hand, even if it's history's worst foreshadowing;
想像したら 鼓動が聞こえたんだ
When I imagined it, I could hear my heartbeat.
作り込んだ道なんて 点滅したバッドエンド
A paved-out path is just a blinking bad end.
君が教えてくれていたんだ
You were the one who taught me that.
夢を散々掛け合わせ 時にはそうそう間違って
Mixing our dreams together, sometimes making mistakes—
それも良し、気にせずに 何度でも挑もう
that's fine too, let's take on the challenge again and again without worrying.
だって I know myself. 意味のない評価で世界比べないで
Because I know myself. Don't compare the world by meaningless evaluations.
叶えたい本音は すべてを包み込む太陽
The true feelings we want to fulfill are a sun that embraces everything.
いっそ月日の方角をめがけて 立ち塞かる壁を登って
Let's aim toward the direction of the moon and sun, climb the walls blocking our way,
刻んでいきたいな そして次に望む
and carve them into history, then look forward to what we wish for next:
後悔しない未来
a future with no regrets.
躓いて視界が 何も見えなくなっても
Even if you stumble and your vision becomes obscured so you can't see anything,
振り向いて笑える そんな場所がある
there's a place where you can turn back and smile.
戦ったの日々も 夢を散々掛け合わせて
Even the days we fought, mixing our dreams together—
時にはそうそう間違って それも良し、気にせずに
sometimes making mistakes, that's fine too, without a care,
何度も挑もう いつも Be yourself 試さないとほら
let's challenge it again and again. Always "Be yourself", if you don't try, look—
何も始まらない
nothing will ever begin.
ささやかな勇気で 明日を変えるまでもっと
With modest courage, until we change tomorrow even more,
意味のない評価で世界比べないで
don't compare the world by meaningless evaluations.
叶えたい本音は すべてを包み込む太陽
The true feelings we want to fulfill are a sun that embraces everything.
いっそ月日の方角をめがけて 立ち塞かる壁を登って
Let's aim toward the direction of the moon and sun, climb the walls blocking our way,
刻んでいきたいな そして次に望む
and carve them into history, then look forward to what we wish for next:
後悔しない未来
a future with no regrets.
初めから僕らは繋がっていたんだ
We were connected right from the very beginning.
引力で出会えた
We met through gravity.
はじめから僕らは 繋がっていたんだ引力で
From the very beginning, we were connected by gravity
出逢えたのは必然 君も気づいているのかな
Meeting each other was inevitable. Are you aware of it too?
遥か宇宙から見たぼくらは まるでちっぽけな星屑
Seen from the distant cosmos, we are just tiny stardust
君と出逢えた瞬間に 僕ら星座になれたの
The moment I met you, we were able to become a constellation
時間を超えて don't stop 未来へ
Transcending time, don't stop towards the future
二つ重ねて 超絶ミラクル
Stacking two together, a transcendent miracle
誰も止められない魔法
A magic that no one can stop
レベチな僕らの銀河へ party night
To our next-level galaxy, party night
wow oh
ふたりはdestiny 引力に引かれて光るclarity
We are destiny, drawn by gravity, shining clarity
ドキドキして愛してねっ、ワクワクして 2人のgravity
Fluttering and loving, excited, our gravity
感情のままに so dance music
Following our emotions, so dance music
すれ違いもまたgroovy
Even misunderstandings are groovy
始めようぜ僕らのgravity
Let's start our gravity
見つめていて朝が来るまで yeah！！
Keep looking until morning comes, yeah!!
これがいわゆる完全無欠なillusion
This is what you call a flawless illusion
まさに完璧なfusion 歌い踊ればsolution
Truly the perfect fusion, singing and dancing is the solution
ここは僕たちのregion みんなの力が重なり広がる
This is our region, everyone's powers overlapping and expanding
たった1つのuniverse
Into just one universe
ねえちょっと泣いたって 明日は晴れる take it easy
Hey, even if you cried a bit, tomorrow will be clear, take it easy
1人でいないでhold on 繋がるいつでも未来へ let's meet up
Don't be alone, hold on, always connected to the future, let's meet up
wow oh
二人のシンパシー 求め合う鼓動が今best ever
Our sympathy, our beating hearts seeking each other is now best ever
見逃さないで感じてさあ業になって
Don't miss it, feel it, and become karma
これぞインフィニティ 考える前let's try doing
This is infinity, before thinking let's try doing
ドジ踏んでもご愛嬌で これからが僕らのgravity
Even if we stumble, it's endearing, from here on is our gravity
ついてきて辿り着くまで yeah！！
Follow us until we reach it, yeah!!
ah 何回でも星座を作るよ 2人で 時空のそらへ 世界へ 待ってて未来へ
ah No matter how many times we'll make a constellation together, into the sky of spacetime, to the world, wait for the future
wow oh
ふたりはdestiny 強くなる絆はまだso growing
We are destiny, our growing bond is still so growing
ドキドキして愛してねっ、ワクワクして 2人のgravity
Fluttering and loving, excited, our gravity
勘違いだらけでもalright つまづいてもまだgroovy
Even full of misunderstandings alright, even if we trip still groovy
始めようぜ僕らのgravity
Let's start our gravity
見つめていて朝が来るまで yeah！！
Keep looking until morning comes, yeah!!
始めようぜ僕らのgravity 見つめていて朝が来るまで yeah！！
Let's start our gravity, keep looking until morning comes, yeah!!
昼公演のみんなに！
To everyone at the daytime show!
せーの！
Ready, go!
お疲れ様でした！
Thank you for your hard work!
ありがとうございます！
Thank you very much!
ということで、SorAZメジャーデビューライブ「First Gravity」アットクラブチッタ、昼公演にお越しいただき、ありがとうございます！
With that said, thank you for coming to the SorAZ Major Debut Live "First Gravity" at CLUB CITTA', daytime show!
ありがとうございます！
Thank you!
みんな盛り上がってますかー？
Is everyone getting hyped?
全力で楽しんでますかー？
Are you enjoying yourselves with all your might?
全体とも見えてるよ！ 見えてるよ！ 声援の皆も見えてるよ！
We can see all of you! We can see you! We can see everyone cheering too!
ありがとうございます！
Thank you!
いやあ、昼公演だよ。昼公演やってきましたね。
Man, it's the daytime show. We've done the daytime show.
夕方だ。夕方だ。でもだんだん日が暮れていくから。夕方だ。はい。
It's evening. It's evening. But it's gradually getting dark. It's evening. Yep.
あ、お水美味しいタイム。美味しかった？美味しかった。またみんなの力で甘くなっとわ。ありがと。
Ah, delicious water time. Was it delicious? It was delicious. With everyone's power, it got sweet. Thanks.
みんなの力でそらちゃんのお水が甘くなっておりますが。はい。
With everyone's power, Sora-chan's water has become sweet. Yep.
ということで、そういえばじゃあ、ちょっと聞きたいことがあるんですけど。
So that reminds me, I have something I want to ask you all.
なに？
What is it?
みんな、昼公演に...
Everyone, to the daytime show...
「来てくれたよ」っていう人、いますかー？
Is anyone here who came and said, "I'm here for you"?
ありがとうございます！
Thank you very much!
夜公演、今回が初めてだよっていう人ー！
Is there anyone attending their first evening show today?
はーい！
Hii!
夜公演配信で見たよっていう人ー！
Is there anyone who watched the evening show on stream?
あ、配信見てくれてくれたんだ、思いますね、ありがとうございます！
Thank you so much to everyone watching the stream!
と言うわけで、えー、恒例のお知らせがあります。
And now, we have our usual announcement.
現在、YouTubeでご覧の皆様、
To everyone currently watching on YouTube,
えー、ここまでが無料配信となります！
the free broadcast ends here!
まだ来たばかり！ まだ来たばかり！
We just got here! We just got here!
まあね、オープニングありまして、
Well, we had the opening,
えと、せーのでと、SUWOTOと、二人でDestinyとやってきましたが、
and performed "SUWOTO" and "Destiny" together,
はい、無料配信はここまでということで、
but the free broadcast ends here.
続きはぜひ、配信チケット、ポチとな？ポチとな？
For the rest, please get a stream ticket—click? click?
ここに、あるよ、ここ！
It's right here, here!
ありますので、ぜひぜひ、えーこの後続きも
So we'd love for you to keep watching
見ていってくださると嬉しいです、よろしくお願いします！
the rest after this! Thank you so much!
お願いしまーす！
Please do!
はい、というわけで、はい。
Yes, so, yes.
はい、なんだろうね。
Yes, I wonder what.
冒頭無料はこちらで終了です。本編続きをご視聴されたい方は、チケットぴあにてご購入お願いします。
The free preview ends here. To watch the rest of the main show, please purchase tickets on Ticket Pia.